<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Line and Pull</title>
    <description>Art, Design, Illustration &amp; Photography</description>
    <link>http://localhost:8080/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:8080/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:57:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creative Diversity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s only early summer, and it’s already been filled with creative inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/creative-diversity/feeling-inspired.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sue Jarman&quot; title=&quot;Feeling Inspired - Sue Jarman&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As much as possible I’ve been cycling my way from place to place, weather permitting, on the rather clunky and rattling Santander bikes. Although I promised, to those I roped in along the way, that there were no steep hills, there were, sorry Faye!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have been enjoying catching up with all the new graduates’ work - navigating my way through a sea of thought provoking visual inspiration - always one of the highlights of summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s always great seeing how briefs’ and trends are interpreted, and how new materials and processes lead and drive this. And although I love digital techniques and processes, I also work with traditional drawing, painting and printing, as part of the development and the end product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It can therefore feel overwhelming when you see so much digitally produced work at every turn – so much, that you end up by craving just more diversity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s probably because of this, that I find myself drawn to some of the traditional hand-worked crafts and processes. I always love wonderfully rich sketchbooks, full of drawings, workings and experimentations that tell a story behind the work; also work that demonstrate an in-depth knowledge of a sampling, pushing processes and techniques; and then work that seamlessly combines technology and the traditional effortlessly, or so it seems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So obviously, the pick of the best, of the new work I’ve seen recently reflect this - some beautifully produced hand painted and printed textiles from Edinburgh College of Art, that you had to touch, sorry; animation at the Royal College, where hand painted storytelling was brought to life with computer software; and finally some fantastic ceramics at Central Saint Martins with shapes, textures and surfaces to die for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talking of ceramics, I also managed to visit the Grayson Perry exhibition at the Serpentine, and yes, marvel at the brilliant work, but also his fantastically packed sketchbooks, wow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/creative-diversity/scarf-man.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sue Jarman&quot; title=&quot;Scarf Man - Sue and Joel&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And finally, I must not leave out a fun afternoon drawing and painting with my nephew. And our joint effort portrait, ‘Man in a Scarf’ is, apparently, clearly influenced by my style, I don’t know what they mean!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2017/06/30/creative-diversity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2017/06/30/creative-diversity/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Splash of Colour</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The role of a creative is a balancing act - a good mix of client lead projects/briefs’, the continuous updating of your skills, being inspired by what’s happening around you, keeping up with other artists’ and designers’ work, and of course networking!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You never really stop thinking art, design, creative… and new ideas arrive at any time of the day or night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travel and journeys are always good germinators - discovering new things and being receptive is easier when you are look at things afresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/splash-of-colour/salo-gallery-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Irma Salo Jaeger&quot; title=&quot;Irma Salo Jaeger&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So during a recent visit to Norway, looking to fill two or three hours with something more stimulating than being sat in a crowded airport lounge, wishing I was still skiing, I decided to visit the Heine Onstad Kunstsenter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This contemporary art gallery/sculpture park (opened in 1968) sits on a 140 acre wooded plot, on the coast just outside Oslo – a beautiful setting and space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gallery was hosting a retrospective of ‘Irma Salo Jaeger’s work’ – she’s described as a ‘master of colour’ and as someone who’s ‘made an indelible mark on modernist painting’. The work was mainly painting, low relief collage, with a few 3D colour automata&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work was stunning, and included a series of calm, geometrics in muted and earthy pastels. This was followed by a body of more vibrant pieces – all saturated and lively with a juxtaposition of geometrics, curves and expressive marks. Then the more recent work, with a graphic and mathematical feel, using limited colours – sharp and strong, but still wonderfully vibrant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a complete contrast to a week of snowy mountains and skiing – probably one of the reasons why it left a strong and colourful mark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see more about the Heine Onstad Kunstsenter at &lt;a href=&quot;http://henieonstadsanatorium.no&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;highlight-link&quot;&gt;www.henieonstadsanatorium.no &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2017/04/06/splash-of-colour/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2017/04/06/splash-of-colour/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion &amp; Form</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Being visually inspired by a recent trip to Copenhagen, and with it feeling decidedly
Spring-like at the moment I started thinking about colour, trends and fashion, well it is London Fashion Week!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And on this note my highlight of the week has to be Burberry’s exhibition at Makers House, Soho.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AW17 sees Burberry’s chief executive officer Christopher Bailey working with the Henry Moore Foundation – using this iconic British artist’s work as inspiration - his drawings, his sculptures, his colours,
his observations from nature…  to inspire what is brilliant and wonderful design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/fashion-form/burberry-capes-sculpture.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Henry Moore Sculpture, Burberry Capes &amp;amp; Design Sketches&quot; title=&quot;Henry Moore Sculpture, Burberry Capes &amp;amp; Design Sketches&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image 1: Looking at the Burberry Capes through a Henry Moore scuplture. Image 2: Burberry design sketches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The atmosphere inside Makers House was delightful - informally friendly with visitors and staff chatting, sharing and commenting
on the fashion, the designs, and the art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s obviously nothing new using art to inspire fashion, and this body of work is a perfect fit for the concept of
going back to nature, bringing the outside in, renewal and not to mention the obvious crossover with fashion and sculpture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The collection features beautifully designed lace that uses the surface textures of Moore’s sculptures to inform the intricate designs;
the use of wool is a direct reference to Moore’s sheep drawings, made from his Hertfordshire studio; and not forgetting the exquisitely
executed capes packed with stitch and textile processes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favourite’s, too many to mention, do include a cotton boiler suit with lace shoulder detailing, inspired by the artist’s overalls
and work-wear; and then there’s the ‘Reclining Figures Print’ capturing the draughtsmanship quality of Moore’s sketches;
and the beautiful fashion development sketches from the Burberry team’s creative process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/fashion-form/burberry-print-boilersuit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Burberry Fashion and Print&quot; title=&quot;Burberry Fashion and Print&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image 1: Burberry’s ‘Reclining Figures Print’ on cotton. Image 2: Burberry’s blue boiler suit with lace detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were also asymmetrical references taken from the sculptural forms, with some beautifully crafted men’s brogues championing this. And this
attention to detail even went as far as the ceiling of the exhibition space, with a clear roof being installed just for the show, allowing the sculptures to be viewed, as they were original intended, in as much natural light as possible!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A beautiful continuum - art echoing landscape and human form, and then garments repopulating natural
and urban environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Celebrating and championing brilliant design and craftsmanship in a fast paced technology driven culture is important – it’s refreshing, rejuvenating and really important we don’t lose sight of preserving balance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need tactile, need physical objects, and need human interaction working simultaneously and in partnership with digital experiences – there’s room for both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My work embraces both - I wouldn’t have it any other way!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am feeling rejuvenated and creatively inspired!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2017/02/24/Fashion-&-Form/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2017/02/24/Fashion-&-Form/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Black and White Images</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This month’s Creative Review magazine had, as usual, loads of interesting articles, but the one that caught my eye was on the 2016 
Pirelli calendar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shot by Annie Leibovitz, printed in black and white - it breaks free from the calendars more recent formats. Leibovitz’s aim was 
to produce images that celebrated female achievement and that were both strong and natural. “I thought of women I admired. I still 
can’t believe the women who agreed to do it” she said. I’m guessing mutual respect, admiration and knowing they’d be in safe hands 
played a big part in their decisions to participate in the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leibovitz has a knack or just an innate talent for capturing human depth. These portraits (and her work in general) dig’s deep, 
capturing souls and external aesthetic. These images don’t disappoint on any level, they’re dramatic, beautiful and strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s the very obvious, physical strength and boldness portrayed with Serena Williams’ image. But then in complete contrast are the 
images of Ava Duvernay and Yao Chen – both with similar poses, with direct eye contact, engaging with the viewer - but there’s where 
the similarity ends.  Both portraits project confidence, determination and strength but in their own very personal and unique 
ways – I love the way each comes across.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I obviously can’t publish any of the calendar photographs but you can see a selection of them
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.harpersbazaar.com.sg/19882/your-first-look-at-the-2016-pirelli-calendar&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;highlight-link&quot;&gt;here &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black and white images just cut to the chase for me, there’s less room to hide, and so much more depth with portraits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were also some really nostalgic and atmospheric architectural photographs at the Charles and Ray Eames exhibition at the Barbican 
last week – again in black and white. The architectural documentation of their projects is beautifully nostalgic artwork in itself. I’m 
in awe of their diverse and influential talent – architecture, furniture, graphic design…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love the Barbican – so took the opportunity to take a few pictures, soak up the atmosphere and get architecturally inspired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/barbican-inspiration.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Barbican Inspiration&quot; title=&quot;Barbican Inspiration&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image 1: Modernist architectural patterns at the Barbican. Image 2: Barbican inspired new work. ©Sue Jarman&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And finally, what made me smile this week? – Well, my sister had a spiritual reading done in which I briefly featured, being 
described as her ‘wacky sister’. Wasn’t sure if this was meant as a complement but… As there are loads of different definitions 
of ‘wacky’, but I’m definitely going with the Cambridge Dictionary’s version, someone who’s ‘unusual in a pleasing and exciting or 
silly way’ – that’s me!!!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2016/02/12/Black-and-White-Images/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2016/02/12/Black-and-White-Images/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Canals, Rivers and Atmosphere</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On my way to the Affordable Art Fair, I stopped to enjoy some misty and atmospheric views up the Thames, off of Chelsea Bridge. Almost 
like going back in time, it felt almost Dickensian. One of my show highlights was a brilliant charcoal, ‘Pool Study’ by Patsy McArthur. 
Her bathers suspended in a beautifully transparent weightlessness, with light reflecting and dancing on their skin and the surrounding 
space. There’s just something wonderful about black and white drawings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/pool-study.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pool Study&quot; title=&quot;Pool Study&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image: ‘Pool Study’by Patsy McArthur - charcoal on paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A surprise find - I didn’t think that a trip to source some bathroom tiles would take me aboard a fantastic canal barge. The 
rentable accommodation, now on my places to stay list, was moored outside Bert &amp;amp; May’s tile showroom, Bethnal Green. It included a 
log burner and a decadently tiled shower room. I could easily live on board.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/barge-interior.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Barge Interior&quot; title=&quot;Barge Interior&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image: Bert and May’s barge, Regents Canal, Hackney, London.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am working on some drawings at present: looking to create some somber and dark imagery of horses, along the lines of my ghosts 
and shadows illustrations. Can’t seem to do cute and fluffy, tend to enjoy dark and scary image making, not sure what says about me!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/horse-comp.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ghosts and Shadows&quot; title=&quot;Ghosts and Shadows&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image: Horse Images from my ‘Ghosts and Shadows’ series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to complete my water theme, with a good pinch of atmosphere this month, ‘River’, what a great, refreshingly different 
crime drama. I’m just soaking up the cinematography, one of those you need to watch more than once to fully appreciate it on all 
levels. I love moody, gritty and atmospheric imagery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visually and creatively it’s been a very monochromatic month for me.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2015/11/18/Canals,-Rivers-&-Atmosphere/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2015/11/18/Canals,-Rivers-&-Atmosphere/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello Autumn</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Summer’s well and truly over and I luckily caught a few late summer rays a couple of weeks ago, in Devon. With a mix of 
cycling, coastal swims, good coffee and some design inspiration, I feel refreshed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salcombe had some diverse creative offerings, from Will Bees Bespoke leather accessories in soft pastel leathers, 
(I’m afraid I had to buy something!!!) to ‘The Drang Gallery’ where I saw a lovely lino cut, ‘Morning’ by Gary Hume, 
which had this shimmering, almost hazy quality to it, and then some screen prints by Sir Peter Blake, who I can’t seem 
to go anywhere at the moment without stumbling across, not that I’m complaining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/blake-hume.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sir Peter Black &amp;amp; Gary Hume&quot; title=&quot;Sir Peter Black &amp;amp; Gary Hume&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Images: ‘Regents Park The Runaway Donkeys’ by Sir Peter Blake, and ‘Morning’ by Gary Hume&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I had a bit of a Victoriana day last Thursday, with a visit to 100% Design at Olympia, it’s new location, with 
Earls Court Exhibition Centre now being closed, very sad. Then later, at Alexandra Palace to see Florence and the Machine, 
a brilliant performance, a stunning voice and some great 70’s style fashion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve just completed some illustrative postcards, capturing some people and their favourite holiday destinations. As well 
as designing a new website for http://www.archbuildingconsultancy.co.uk, the colour palette being a particular hit with the client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/postcards.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Holiday Postcards&quot; title=&quot;Holiday Postcards&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Images: ‘Rosalind’ &amp;amp; ‘Keith’ postcards from my ‘Holiday Postcards Series’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And finally, I Boris Biked to Tent London last Saturday, which was, as always, brilliant!!!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2015/10/02/Hello-Autumn/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2015/10/02/Hello-Autumn/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Open Swimming</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;And you’re thinking, what place does open swimming have in my creative blog?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only do I find it a great way to think, get inspired, to feel rejuvenated, you can also get completely immersed with the rhythm, apart from when your goggles start leaking. The sound of the water rushing past and the air bubbles boiling are your soundtrack. It’s a self propelled journey, and for me all journeys are generators of new ideas, the only problem is, you have to find creative ways of memorising the ideas without having a notebook to hand. You’re part of two worlds simultaneously, stopping occasionally to take it all in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s also a nostalgic feel and mood to it all, that overlaps with some current personal influences of mine, Art Deco meets 1930s 
bathing meets fashion – as long as you ignore the competitive triathlon images that is!!! Probably why I’m feeling that open swimming, the apparent ‘trend for 2015’ is everywhere at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/swim_edit_suejarman.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Swimming Edit&quot; title=&quot;Swimming Edit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few of my favourite finds this month have been a tiny bathing cartoon from a 1956 ‘Punch’ magazine, a railway poster 
from a 1934 art review catalogue, and the fabulous front cover of ‘Suitcase’ magazine. Although created several 
decades apart they all just sit seamlessly together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Punch cartoon - Edwards, May 1956.
Troon poster - McCorquodale Studio for L.M.S. Railway, 1934.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2015/08/17/Open-Swimming/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2015/08/17/Open-Swimming/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Maps and Wild Spaces</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/knoydart_sketch_illustration_sue_jarman.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Knoydart Sketchbook&quot; title=&quot;Knoydart Sketchbook&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not sure how I managed it but a long planned trip to Knoydart in Scotland magically coincided with a window of fantastic hot 
weather, enabling me to see breathtaking views from the mountain tops, bag a few Munro’s and fit in some sketching. An added 
highlight was seeing a pod of dolphins. It’s a wonderful place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/soho_map_illustration_sue_jarman.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Soho Map&quot; title=&quot;Soho Map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Been going back to my cartographic roots (not routes) this month, producing some illustrated maps, the one of Soho lunch spots 
is my favourite. Have eaten in the oasis of Soho Square a few times, but haven’t tried the others yet!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hand drawn and illustrated maps are really popular, and everywhere at the moment, think they’re just a refreshing change 
from Streetmap or Google, that we all use and love, but variety is good…, it’s just more interesting to pick up something 
that’s fun, personalised and just has a particular insight or focus in to an area. If you’re in need of some cartographic 
inspiration I can recommend looking at ‘A Map of the World’ by ‘gestalten’, there’s a map in there for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also managed to pop in to ‘Pick Me Up’ at Somerset House. I was really taken by the work of illustrator Laura Callaghan, 
with her complex and detailed illustrated observations and screenprints.  There was also something really interesting and 
haunting about Zoe Taylors pen and ink drawings too.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2015/05/26/Maps-and-Wild-Spaces/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2015/05/26/Maps-and-Wild-Spaces/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The World In Full Colour</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I feel like the world is in full colour this month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/lounge-party-with-text2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Summer Lounge Party&quot; title=&quot;Summer Lounge Party&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve completed my Summer Lounge Party illustration, inspired by summer parties and celebrations.
And everywhere you look there’s colour and pattern, it just raises everybody’s mood.
Am really looking forward to buying some 70’s inspired fashion too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also discovered the work of the Norwegian painter Peder Balke, at the National Gallery in London.
His bleak and isolated seascapes, with large stormy skies really capture a sense of space, isolation and wild Scandinavian scenery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A real highlight was an evening listening to the journalist Christina Lamb, roving Foreign Affairs Correspondent for the Sunday Times.
She talked about her career, her experiences and some of the people she’s worked with and met along the way.
It was a really interesting and inspiring evening.
An added bonus was it enabled me to get some fantastic views over London, at dusk, from the top of the ‘Mini Shard’, really beautiful!!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2015/04/14/The-World-In-Full-Colour/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2015/04/14/The-World-In-Full-Colour/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Above The Clouds</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/lake_district_sue_jarman_blog_march_2015.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Above The Clouds&quot; title=&quot;Above The Clouds&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Managed to get above the clouds this month, in the snowy Lake District, just before spring kicked in, my favourite season.
Whilst there I popped into Keswick and I stumbled across ‘Cherrydidi’, a great shop selling a mix of artists’ and designers’ work,
and then a gallery, with some beautiful printmaking by Margaret Morris.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/imgs/blog/fashion_pose_figures_ink_blog_march_2015.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lounge Party&quot; title=&quot;Lounge Party&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been producing some infographics, some pen and ink figure illustrations, and dipping my toe into some HTML coding,
well editing at least!!! And I’ve started animating some of my illustrations, love a bit of variety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And after a long wait, my ‘H is for Hawk’ by Helen Macdonald arrived, and although, only a few pages in, I’m hooked already.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8080/2015/03/13/Above-The-Clouds/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/2015/03/13/Above-The-Clouds/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
